desk fan

she sits pretty like an adequate wife
they make them larger too, but it would cost too much
so she stands like a Pomeranian chained to a post 
pleasuring the man who uses her 
demanding to be flicked in the stingy air 
nothing to lose, but something was lacking
like the eerie glow of infinitude to a mortal man 
demanding to use pleasure to chase down death
blades twirling like a-cup-a breasts, a beauty so robust
