kombucha


it's that sick bubbling up again of what can't possibly be something 
that aching between your boobs it wants to come out, it will come out
sometimes its you but sometimes its ephemeral as you are not 
fleeting although sometimes fleeing, i digress, the sway of moments 
is gravel sifting through the fingers leaving a dusty varnish 
that smells like rust and this smells so repulsive this thing slipping 
beneath your chest racing through the golgi body that is your body

the cackles. the tussles. the bus that flipped over on I-80S. sucking her 
nipple.

it’s some type of turn on, when your steak, is somehow transfigured, 
into something smooth
when the moon tips over and spills into being and your cheeks are tinted 
embarrassment 
for the light bolsters the slivers, cracks, brown smudges, purple 
vessels, the edge of his/her skirt 
tucked into the crotch, by accident

as if, we're all here for a purpose. 

(my eutopia) in fact, one day it was rather mild in a slightly different 
frame and i spoke openly of vocation to a sea of sultry zombies. I was 
going to prude shame. It was brilliant, I thought, to vandalize these 
billboards with giant gaping pussies. I mean giant pink clams. And the 
toilets; there would be a plethora of designer toilets inside every 
unisex bathroom to be used for hot shit together.

and we would crap, and cry and laugh �til our brain vessels explode
with orgiastic swagger we'd zip on our cow disguises and tip each other 
over 
and moo and moan follow the light to the butcher's shack 

our souls: xenophobia; homesickness, homophobia. the fear of looking into
another's eyes and seeing yourself. 

the genius looks into himself and sees everyone as a responsibility to
the shepherd; he is a sheep in neon orange. god, they said is onto-
theologic, you must trust him because your experience is recycled 
excrement. 
the shepherd said and kept saying and cars and cotton gins and bicycles 
surged from his foaming mouth.

its peppery and perverted and stagnant like malaria infested waters and
you drink it to stay sick 
they tell you, it's better to die young that way in derivatives and 
integrals and christianity to be an ultimate telos of a bigger tutelage

sometimes its runny and it comes out quick and easy and you write it down 
on paper 
and it flies into the horizon, buzzing and lifting, through binoculars it 
disappears
others are lofty logs, breaking through membranes with a snag, leaving a 
fissure 
they sink like sediment, resting next to pebbles and fervid dissertations





