ode to the conservation of mass morals 



but i want to be good so I sit up tall and mighty. i stroke the hands of 
my comrades

i am the boy with the cupcake breadth, my butter cream intonation grazing 
multicolored tongues 

my friends are dressed in optimistic periwinkle and lusting crimson, 
stroking each otherÔøΩs tits and thrusting hips

this is New york, this is condemned to be free. as I inch towards the 
right, their empathy is platform heels on bubble wrap 

I am human, I am humanized. i agree to turn over what makes me tall and 
proud. i am itty bitty.  

my hate resides in a mason jar within my heart. it is invisible. it 
smells like the sour diesel on my armoire. 

i look for the devil in my love's eyes. i want to be penetrated by 
bigots. i am sick, i am horny. 

my finger nails are 4 a.m black. i look for skin grey and thin, 
incandescence coagulated into a sticky cluster in the eyes. i want to 
harvest the golden flower. i want to feel mutilated.

Steven Pasquale would be an example of a good fuck most likely. i am a 
heated right wing. i blast bluejays with my unregulated AK. i watch their 
wings crumple and spray like confetti.

i want to feel pity. i want to taste our weakness. i want us all to fall. 
i want to feel the falling before that.  

i have charmed my way into the hearts of kind people; its a sick 
repugnance adorned in shimmery thread.

their hands are supple and insulating. their hands are insulting. their 
hands hold Bic pencils. their mouthes hoard loose leaf symbols. their 
skin is melting white like our ice caps. 

a black hole is a succinct little particle of nothing. it is 
extraordinarily simple; far too simple for light. 

gay may be a choice; hate may be not a choice. i choose rest; i am 
sleepy. the charcoal sky is a haughty curtain. i am ensnared. i am 
unconcerned. 

i am lost and alone. my body is nestled warm and cozy between two 
figures. i am watching myself have sex. 

we are russian nesting dolls. we grow smaller and disappear. we are 
offspring of Hasbro.

you want some splendid language for your low fat latte: ÔøΩburn your 
lipids. lo, a blow thatÔøΩs low and also a job.ÔøΩ we all see fat.

my genitals are the silicone valley. my brain is bloated with salty 
fallacy. i am a thinking ion; i am incomplete; i am refracted; i am 
volatile; i am an aggregate

as we eclipse spacetime, our vocal cords vibrate faster; resonation. like 
the tidal wave in my slumber hours, archetypes rinse over our toes, 
glazing the logicianÔøΩs spectacles in impervious calcification. 

i am blinded within little nano orgasms prickling the surface of my 
breathing flesh. the waking life is a shrieking whisper. we all sift 
through each otherÔøΩs paths. occasionally a pedestrian collision occurs. 
its a robotic swivel of the neck and a redirected vector.













